VINCENT HARTANTO

Frontend Developer

Jakarta, Indonesia

vincenthartanto.github.io

vincenthartantoo.work@gmail.com

PROFILE

Graduated in computer science major with 3.57 GPA. In my professional career, I have two roles such as full stack engineer and IT support specialist. In those two years, I did bug fix and created two applications such as ticketing and mobile hospital application. While I have enjoyed working on both the front-end and back-end of web development projects, I have recently discovered a strong passion for front-end development.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

❖ Full Stack Engineer, Accelist Lentera Indonesia

..... Mar 2020 — Mar 2021

Tangerang

- I had the opportunity to work on a challenging and rewarding project, where I developed hospital app using
 Flutter and ASP. NET technologies. This app has a various kind of features that helps patient find the nearest
 hospital, booking doctor, video calling with doctor and buying medicine for doctors
- My responsibility of this development were making the user interface of the mobile app and creating database for the app. I have created various of API to enable the main features of the apps.
- Full Stack Engineer and IT support, Accelist Lentera Indonesia

..... Mar 2021 — Mar 2022

Tangerang

- As a Full Stack Engineer and IT Support, I have had the opportunity to work on diverse range of project that
 required me to troubleshoot and resolve complex issues. I had fixed data optimization and UI Bug fixes.
- My accomplishment as a Full Stack engineer was the development of ticketing application, which greatly
 improved the efficiency of documenting bug fixed for our IT Support Team. As a result, we have significant
 reduction of time documenting the bug fixes, overall the productivity in IT support Team increased
 significantly.

EDUCATION

♣ Binus University
Computer Science
Sep 2017 — Mar 2021
Jakarta

 As a 3.57 GPA Computer Science graduate in 3,5 years. My excellent work ethic, commitment to excellence, and enduring passion for technology and innovation are evident in my academic results.

<u>SKILLS</u>	
SQL	React
CSS	HTML5
Git	JavaScript
Git	JavaScript

CIZIT I C